Sync & corrections by Blue-Bird™
Srt2smi by Blue-Bird™
Life Foundation Control, this is LF1.
The specimens are secured,
and we're heading home.
Roger, LF1. You are a go for reentry.
Copy that. Initiating reentry sequence.
Point-four by 103-point... Shit.
Seal it off. Seal it off!
LF1, Mission Control.
You're breaking up. Please repeat.
Mayday, Mayday, LF1!
- Mayday!
- LF1, Mission Control.
Please repeat.
LF1, Mission Control. Please repeat.
I don't want to have to wait
for full clean-up just to get
- a status report.
- We're collecting this data
- as quickly as possible.
- That's not good enough.
Okay, maybe you can tell me
what happened.
There was some kind of breach.
One of the astronauts
- sent a distress call.
- What about the crew?
- We're still investigating.
- Where did it go down?
It's 20 kilometers west of Sibu.
Did we at least retrieve
all of the samples?
No. We have three of them.
One of the organisms
got out of containment,
and it's missing.
We don't know which one.
What is she saying?
One of the astronauts is still alive.
That's Jameson.
- Morning, sunshine.
- What?
I'm awake.
Missed me.
- I'm awake.
- Here you go.
- You can have it back.
- Thank...
You're wearing a suit. Yes!
- I love it when you wear the suit.
- Thank you.
I have depositions today
in the Life Foundation case.
Hey, let me know how your meeting goes.
My meeting?
Shit. Yeah.
My meeting.
Coffee.
- You are perfect.
- Thank you.
Hey, you know what...
You know what night
- it is tonight, right?
- Date night.
So, I will pick you up around 6:00.
And please do not forget your helmet.
I'm glad that you like it,
'cause I plan on wearing it
at our wedding.
That's hot.
Feed the cat.
I will.
I love you!
Love you, too. Feed the cat.
Eddie Brock with boots on the ground
today in the Mission District,
chasing a lead into some...
Everybody knows how
our Silicon Valley overlords
- at Google and Facebook...
- Last time, I was poking around
asking uncomfortable questions...
Homelessness is only increasing
into the thousands...
Eddie Brock here reporting
today from downtown Oakland,
where massive demonstrations
have taken over the streets.
I've been chasing
this real-estate bribery story
for a few weeks now.
- This is gonna piss you off.
- ...all being strong-armed...
Medical examiner has yet
to determine cause of death,
due to the condition of the body,
but you don't wind up
at the bottom of a landfill
due to natural causes,
so it seems that the city
doesn't care about these people
any more than the killer does.
I'm Eddie Brock,
and this is The Brock Report.
Hey, Richard!
- Lookin' good!
- Eddie, you can't park there, bro.
Come on, man.
There's no such thing as can't.
How'd she do?
Berkeley. Brown. MIT.
- She's got a scholarship, bro.
- What'd I tell you?
You told me what?
- No such thing as can't.
- Eddie.
The bike.
MIT!
You know what I love about this view?
- It never gets old.
- Yeah, well...
Height's not really my thing.
But... What's the deal?
- I got you the big one, exclusive.
- Yeah? Who?
Carlton Drake.
- Carlton Drake?
- The man's a visionary.
He wants to talk about his rockets,
assure everyone they're safe,
that the crash was an anomaly.
He's seriously off.
I'm gonna level with you.
Carlton Drake could buy us
with his pocket cash,
turn this building into his own garage
if he so wished.
Now, you're just gonna ask him
about his space program,
you're gonna thank him,
and you're gonna bid him a nice day.
He's a crook.
Eddie, when you had nowhere to go,
we gave you a home.
Now, you know we love
the Eddie Brock show.
There isn't a better
investigative reporter working today,
but no one is above the network.
So do me a favor, Eddie,
don't start your shit again.
All right, all right.
- For me.
- All right. I'll do it.
I don't know why he gave me
this assignment, Annie.
It's not what I do.
Well, my mother always told me
that anything in life worth having
would take sacrifice...
Patience...
And be a lot of work.
That's you...
- That's not.
- ...that I'm talking about.
- Nah.
- Yeah.
Well, you're lucky to have me.
To be fair, I'm quite a catch.
That's what my mom told me.
Are you gonna behave yourself tomorrow?
No. No, I'm gonna do my job.
That's what I'm gonna do.
I can't, you know, not do my job.
The guy you work for is a complete...
I don't work for Drake.
I work for my firm,
and my firm works for him.
And I'm sure
that they defend many people
that you don't deem worthy,
but we don't want a repeat.
- A repeat?
- Of the Daily Globe incident.
Really?
Incident? That's not an incident.
- Baby, you were run out of New York.
- I was not. I did not.
I don't want you
run out of San Francisco.
No, I still have currency in New York.
I was going places.
I wasn't running.
In fact, I moved
to San Francisco for you.
- Me?
- You are my home.
You're not so bad yourself, champ.
- Less talking, more kissing.
- All right.
Let's just get the check.
I'm gonna get a drink.
Very soon,
another Life Foundation rocket
will be sent on an exploratory mission.
And that's how, one day,
we might all live in space.
Cool, huh? And now that I've shown you
some of the cool stuff that we do here,
I'm hoping I've inspired
each and every one of you
to go out there
and create things that others
- have only dreamt of.
- Mr. Drake?
It's okay. Don't silence her.
Come here. What's your name?
- Allie.
- It's okay, Allie.
You know,
sometimes that's what people do.
They try and silence
those of us who ask questions.
But you know what? In the end,
we're the ones who change the world.
Take good care of that, Allie.
Guys, this is Dr. Skirth.
- Say hi.
- Hi.
Hello, kids.
Sorry to interrupt,
but it's time to get changed
for your interview.
Yeah. Kids, sorry to leave you.
Allie, you're in charge.
High five up top.
Dr. Skirth will answer Allie's question,
and any others.
- See you next time, guys. Bye!
- Bye!
What do you say, Mr. Drake,
we just start at the beginning?
Born to British parents.
And then at 19,
you discovered a gene therapy
that literally doubles
the life expectancy
- of pancreatic cancer patients.
- Well, actually,
it tripled their life expectancy.
But it's okay.
Okay, 24. That's still extremely young.
All right, you create
- the Life Foundation!
- It didn't happen overnight.
And then... Rockets.
You then decide,
like any normal human being,
that you're gonna go and explore space.
You know what it is?
I have always believed
that space exploration
is crucial in our quest to cure
everything that ails us here on Earth.
But if you think about
everything we've found
in the oceans and on land,
isn't it time to look up there?
To this plethora of untapped resources?
And you have a plethora
of untapped resources, also,
from your pharmaceutical companies
that you're involved with,
you know, to help you realize
- that ambition, I suppose.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
- Full circle.
So, I have to ask, how does that work,
you know, exactly,
the Life Foundation thing?
How does it... How does it...
I don't know, how does it go about,
- say, testing pharmaceuticals?
- Eddie, we're talking
- about the rocket here.
- No, I'm not. I'm not.
I'm talking about the allegations.
- I'm sorry, I don't...
- It says that
your entire empire has been built
- on dead bodies.
- Eddie.
It's true, right?
It says that you recruit
the most vulnerable of us
to volunteer for tests
that more often than not
end up killing people.
Yeah, I'm aware of these rumors online.
There's a lot of fake news
out there these days.
Right. What about the legal cases?
Sorry?
The actual legal cases,
like Sarah Chambers,
- Phil Barclay, Rob MacDonald.
- That's it. Time to go.
Thank you so much for coming
to talk to me, Mr. Brock.
And they're just some
of the people who walked
- through these doors...
- Have a nice day.
- Cut the camera off, please.
- Thank you very much.
- Time is up. Come on.
- They're dead. The Dead...
- Could you show him out, please?
- The Dead Found...
Don't touch me.
The Dead Foundation thing.
- Get out of here, Brock.
- We're not finished.
Yes, you are, Mr. Brock.
Is that a threat?
Have a nice life.
I know what you're going to say, but...
This guy, he is all the way bad, Jack.
- If you just give...
- Who's your source?
- Excuse me?
- Who's your source, Eddie?
I don't have a source, per se.
But I have a hunch.
This isn't the Wild Wild West.
We don't go off half-cocked
based on a hunch.
We do the work.
We substantiate our accusations.
We provide evidence.
You know, for a smart guy,
you really are a dumbass.
You're fired, Eddie.
I can't trust you.
Have a nice life.
- Will just take a second.
- Okay.
Hey.
You are pathologically self-absorbed.
- Annie. Annie, can you talk to me first?
- Your ego requires constant attention,
and you're stubborn as hell.
But I was willing to roll with it,
Eddie, because I loved you.
You "loved" me?
What is that supposed to mean?
What you did got me fired.
You used me.
Annie? Annie.
Oh, my God.
You're beautiful.
Test 36.
Biological interactions between
two different organisms.
These creatures need to bond
with a respiratory host
in order to survive
for any amount of time
in an oxygen-rich environment.
Well, why are all these hosts
showing this hyper-acute rejection?
That's what we're trying to find out.
The bonding process is starting.
It's equalizing.
But why? Why this rabbit?
It's similar to an organ transplant.
Where the donor and recipient
must be an exact match?
- That's correct.
- Okay. So wait, think about it.
If we do achieve symbiosis,
they should be able to survive here,
but also we would
be able to survive there.
"We"?
- Begin human trials.
- It's way too soon
to even begin to think
about something like...
Dr. Skirth, you're at the forefront
of a scientific breakthrough.
I need you to hold your nerve.
All right?
I understand,
but it's an ethical question.
Think of future generations.
Think of your kids.
Hey, how are your kids?
Let's begin human trials.
Good work.
Hey, Jack.
Do you ever feel like your life
is like one monumental screwup?
- Nope.
- Here at the Life Foundation,
- we've always believed...
- Isn't that your buddy?
...in finding the lessons
in our disappointments.
In the months since our rocket failed,
we've learned so much.
Do you think we could,
like, switch him off?
Some people are trying to watch that.
You are, are you?
- Yeah?
- Aren't you Eddie Brock?
I used to be.
We take the same view of progress.
Thrilled to announce
that the Life Foundation
has now begun preparations
on its next launch.
All right, Jack, this is for you.
I do not want you
to spend it all at once.
I'm going to go home
and chase myself around the room,
playing hard to get.
- Hey, Maria.
- Eddie.
- How's it going?
- Righteous, Eddie.
Yeah, we're empty.
Cost you $5.
$5 for a paper that's free?
I walked all the way over
to the vending machine,
got the papers out
and brought 'em back over here,
so you can have 'em
personally delivered to you.
- You did that for me?
- Yes, I did.
- Five bucks.
- That's pretty steep.
Tell you what,
you give me a dollar for a song,
I'll throw in the paper.
I'll tell you what,
I will give you 20 bucks,
but not to sing, all right?
Deal.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
No. You're welcome.
Hey, Mrs. Chen.
- How you doing, Eddie?
- Aches and pains,
you know, aches and pains.
You look like shit.
Excuse me?
And you look as beautiful as ever.
- Jesus.
- Mind is body, Eddie.
Have you been meditating
like I showed you?
- No, I have not. And it does not work.
- It doesn't work,
- because you don't give it a chance.
- No, it doesn't work,
because I bought a DVD off your cousin,
and it was in Mandarin.
Yeah, I don't understand that, either.
See, that right there,
I don't understand what you just said.
That is the problem.
Bottle of whiskey,
and don't forget my change.
Please.
Let's go.
Before the price goes up
for my protection.
The full payment is due.
Now.
Make sure you have my money ready, Chen.
I don't like to wait.
Life hurts, Eddie.
It just does.
I gotta go.
- Okay. Love you, babe.
- See you, babe.
And the state it put him in
What a dick.
To hold his head high
When he really wanna die
And you know
The difference it makes
All that it takes
Is love...
I'm not even asking to staff there.
Why would I do that?
I can't use my name.
I can use a pseudonym.
Any name. Think... You pick a name.
I could be a woman.
Have you seen Tootsie?
I'll call you back.
Okay, I won't. Thank you. Bye.
Realize deeply that the present moment
is all you ever have.
Make the now
the primary focus of your life.
Any action is often better
than no action,
especially if you have been stuck
in an unhappy situation for a long time.
If it is a mistake,
at least you learned something,
in which case it's no longer...
Thank you all
for bringing us to this moment.
Our names will be spoken
long after we are dust.
History starts now.
This is day one.
This is first contact.
Let's get to work.
Establishing subject baseline.
All vital signs are normal.
Put me through.
There's no need to be frightened, Isaac.
There's no need.
Isaac. You know that's a biblical name?
Yes, sir.
God said to Abraham, "Give me your son,
"show me you are willing
to sacrifice the one thing
"most precious to you,"
and Abraham was willing.
You know what's always
impressed me about that story?
It isn't Abraham's sacrifice.
It's Isaac's.
Now, I don't know what kind of God
would ask that of someone,
but it doesn't change anything for me.
Isaac is still the hero of this story.
Look around you. Look at the world.
What do you see? War, poverty,
a planet on the brink of collapse.
I would argue that God has abandoned us.
He didn't keep
his end of the bargain, Isaac,
so now it's down to you and me
to put this right.
And this time, Isaac, we can.
We will.
This time, I will not abandon us.
Yes.
Open it.
What the hell is that? What? No, what...
Please let me... No.
Please, please, please!
His vitals are holding steady.
- Where the hell did it go?
- Incredible.
Where did it go?
Where is it?
Bring in the next volunteer.
You know, I used to be a reporter.
I was...
I was pretty successful,
as well, you know?
Myjob, it required you to...
You know, to follow people
that did not want to be followed
and hide in plain sight.
I mean...
You have to know how to disappear.
I was pretty good, but, you know, you...
Whoever you are, you suck.
Okay.
My name is Dora Skirth.
I need your help.
- I work at the Life Foundation.
- You do?
- Yes.
- Good for you.
We're done.
No...
Mr. Brock, please...
Please listen to me.
Everything that you accused him of,
you were right. It's all true.
- I don't care anymore.
- Really?
Because he's got a lab
filled with poor people,
and they're all signing waivers
that they don't understand,
and he's using them like guinea pigs,
and they are dying.
They are all dying.
- You've seen that?
- Yes.
Come here.
Why would I believe you?
Because it's true.
I believed in him, and I...
I told myself that it was worth it
because we were curing cancer,
but now this is different.
- Something else.
- Go to the cops.
I can't do that.
I'm afraid of what will happen
to my family.
He's a very dangerous man,
and he's a very powerful man...
I know, I know how dangerous he is,
because the very first time
I interviewed him,
just once, I lose my job
the very next day.
I lost my career,
I lost my relationship,
I lost my apartment,
I lost everything I ever cared about.
You know why?
Carlton Drake ruined me. Finished.
Now, if you are who you say you are,
genuinely, and you have proof,
then you should be
very, very, very afraid.
I am.
You need to find yourself another
white knight, Ms. Skirth,
because I am done.
I am done with all of this shit.
What shit?
All of this "saving my fellow man" shit.
All right? Good night.
Eddie?
Well, hey.
Anne, I was just walking by, and...
I saw Mr. Belvedere.
I felt concerned for his welfare, so...
Eddie...
This is Dan.
- Dan, this is Eddie.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- Hey, man.
- Yeah.
- Annie's told me a lot about you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm a big fan of your work.
- Thank you.
- Really?
It's pretty cool,
all the people that he took down.
Yeah, I was one of them.
Well, look, I'll let you guys catch up.
- So I'll see you inside?
- You're the best.
- Really nice meeting you, man.
- You, too.
He has a key. You know he has a key?
Yeah. How else would he get in?
Yeah. Well...
So, what you up to?
You realize that's light-years away
from being any of your business, right?
Hey, well, just asking, you know.
So, is Dan a lawyer?
No, he's a doctor.
Surgeon, actually.
How's Mr. Belvedere, anyway?
I would say that he misses you,
but that would be bullshit, 'cause...
- He's a cat.
- No, because he never liked you.
No, he's a cat,
and cats don't like anyone.
You look good, by the way.
You doing good?
What are you doing here, Eddie?
I'm here 'cause I miss you.
A lot.
You know, we were gonna get married.
That wasn't so long ago,
and now, you know...
I can't really believe that we're not...
Are we gonna try and find our way back?
No, we can't.
You did this, Eddie.
Not Carlton Drake, not the network.
You.
Hello. This is Dr. Skirth.
Yes, Eddie Brock here.
Talk to me.
Are you sure this is gonna work?
Just stay down and shut up, please.
53.5, win-909 RPM.
Overpopulation and climate change.
These are two things
that Drake cannot control.
Yeah, got it, right.
We are literally a generation away
from an uninhabitable Earth.
- Yeah.
- Drake is using his personal rockets
to scout real estate.
You know,
it's a really interesting story,
but we need to just get to the part
where he's killing people.
Drake sent a ship on a recon mission.
On the way back, they found a comet.
A comet?
Onboard computers indicated the presence
of life, of millions of organisms.
Wait, wait, wait, when you say
"millions of organisms,"
- what do you mean?
- We brought back some specimens.
You're talking about aliens?
Like, aliens?
E.T. phone home.
Aliens, yeah.
Yes.
But we don't call them that.
- We call them Symbiotes.
- Symbiotes?
And they cannot survive in
our environment without help.
Drake believes that the union
between human and Symbiote
is the key to our survival,
but not here on Earth.
Drake is trying to put human beings
and aliens together?
So they can live in space?
We call them hosts.
That's nuts, isn't it?
That's completely insane.
Yes. There's no protocol for this thing.
He's just feeding them in.
If the match isn't exact...
Elevators patrol check.
Please, just go in.
Don't touch anything.
- I won't. I won't.
- Go, go, go. I'll take care of him.
Dr. Skirth.
I thought you'd all gone home.
Yes. Well, you know what they say.
Science never sleeps.
- Eddie! It's me. Let me out!
- Maria? Maria?
- Please! Let me out!
- I don't know how to get you...
- Let me out. Out.
- I don't know how.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God! Maria, no! Maria!
Maria! No, Maria, no!
There has been a security breach
in Lab Sector 3.
Oh, no. Maria?
Maria! Shit.
Repeat, this is
a Code Silver security breach.
Freeze!
Got eyes on!
Go!
Go! Go!
Where the hell'd he go?
- I'm not seeing him.
- Fan out.
- Find him.
- Nothing. Nothing yet.
Search Team 4, Search Team 4.
Backtrack 200 feet east.
This is Dora. Leave a message.
Skirth, yeah, it's me. I just got back.
Are you all right?
I haven't heard from you,
so I want to know if you're all right.
But, yeah,
that was a great call on the lab.
You're absolutely right.
Yeah. Listen.
I got a... I got a guy.
I'm gonna call him and...
I got a bunch of photographs.
He will publish those photographs,
but I need you to come with me.
Could you just call me back?
Call me back.
Yeah.
What is wrong with me?
Eddie.
How bad?
It's bad.
Well, we assume the intruder took it.
Took it? Took it?
We don't know what happened.
I want to speak to every man
who was on duty last night.
- Already did, sir.
- But I didn't.
Get it out of my sight.
- Carlton, you need to see this.
- What now?
His blood pressure's back to normal.
Liver functions, too.
I knew it.
See, his body just needed
time to adjust.
I don't want to waste any more time.
I want to up the tests.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Come on.
You're fired.
Find my Symbiote.
Now!
Jesus.
Attention, passengers for Flight 2517
to San Francisco via Hong Kong.
We will be boarding
at gate 9 in 15 minutes.
Please have your boarding passes...
Suzy. Come on, over here.
May I speak to Annie Weying, please?
Can you tell her that it's an emergency?
Food.
Who said that?
No, I'm not talking to you.
Can you please tell me where she is?
Great. Thank you.
Okay...
Yes, Lana for two?
- I'm sorry, sir?
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Sir?
- Yes.
Oh, my God, Eddie.
What are you doing here?
- Annie...
- No, no, no...
No, I have to tell you something.
- No, no, no. Please.
- No, now. I have to.
Work told me you were here.
You're the only person that I trust.
Are you drunk?
Yeah. No,
I broke into the Life Foundation.
- Eddie, you did what?
- Yeah, but I may...
I think I may have been infected.
He's burning up. You're really hot.
Eddie, you look like
you're in a bad way.
I am. I am in a bad way.
Eddie, Jesus!
This is dead.
Dead.
Eddie, sit down.
Okay, all right. Okay.
- Hey, hey, Eddie, Eddie, Eddie.
- Stop that.
- Sir, sir, sir, I'm so sorry.
- Eddie, quit it.
Put it down. Eddie!
Snap out of it!
No.
All right. It's no good.
Bobby, are you all right?
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm a doctor. I'm a doctor.
I'm hot. Is anyone else hot?
Are you hurt?
- Sir, excuse me.
- No!
Wait, where are you going? Eddie?
This is unacceptable.
I'm gonna call the police.
What are you doing? No, please don't.
- No.
- Eddie, please.
Oh, my God.
- Now I'm gonna call the police.
- No, no. Please don't call the police.
Here, call an ambulance.
I'm a doctor. This man is my...
Patient.
It's much better.
You are insane.
- He's killing people.
- Who's killing people?
- Carlton Drake.
- Oh, God, Eddie,
- not this again.
- Yes, he is. He is!
And I have proof!
Hey, Eddie...
Eddie.
Eddie?
Eddie, can you hear me?
This is Dan speaking to you.
Hey, Dan.
- Welcome back.
- Where am I?
You're in the MRI.
Okay, we've given you a little sedative.
- Where is Anne?
- Anne is not here right now.
We're gonna run some tests, okay?
It's gonna be completely painless.
So, you know, just try to stay still.
Relax, and...
Yeah, here we go.
Eddie, what's happening in there?
Eddie, you okay?
Shut it down.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're okay. Yeah.
Coming out. You all right?
- Yeah.
- Here, look at me, look at me.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
All right. Just take a deep breath.
Okay? You're okay.
Yeah.
Now, listen, you're not the first person
to freak out in there.
I get claustrophobic, too.
Dr. Lewis?
Oh, boy. Hey, Mrs. Manfredi.
How are you?
I just saw Morris.
And he's whining and complaining
like an old baby again.
- Good.
- Thank you so much.
Yeah, my pleasure.
Okay, Mrs. Manfredi,
we talked about the dog.
Okay, love the dog.
You can't have the dog.
Sorry. Gemini.
We're gonna get to the bottom of this.
All right? That I can promise you.
But for now, go home, get some rest.
I'll call you when your tests are in.
- All right, thank you.
- Okay? Yep.
- Thank you, Dan. Thank you.
- You got it.
- Hello, Doctor.
- Hi.
Did you have the same reactions
regardless of the temperature...
Good afternoon, Dr. Skirth.
The creature and the host are one.
Everything was fine.
So, why does the human
continue to waste away?
I don't know. We've given him enough
liquid nutrition to feed an elephant.
But the organism is unaffected?
- The Symbiote is thriving.
- Good.
But once again, it's killing the host.
It's consuming his organs.
Watch this.
What are you doing?
You're hurting it. Stop it!
Sounds in the 4,000 to 6,000 hertz
range are very harmful for it.
- Well, then don't make those sounds.
- Okay.
He was stabilizing. What happened?
He's approaching acute liver failure.
We're gonna need another host.
Such poor design.
- Excuse me?
- Human beings.
Sorry to interrupt.
Thought you'd like some good news.
I'm sorry.
Hungry!
Goddamn.
I'm okay. Don't worry about me.
Can I get through, please? Excuse me.
Thank you.
I'm just gonna stay here, all right?
Until the cable car stops.
We're good. All right. Thank you.
Excuse me.
Hey, Anne.
Eddie, hi. How you feeling?
Feeling... I'm sick.
Well, Eddie, you have a parasite.
They're not exactly sure how you got it,
but it would explain the fever.
That would make sense.
Also, I'm hearing a voice.
Auditory hallucinations
are actually very common.
Hey, Dan. How you doing?
I didn't realize
that you were on the call, too.
Yeah, I'm here.
Hey, Dan, would this parasite...
Would it, like, be able to make me,
I don't know...
Like, climb a really, really,
really tall tree,
but super, super fast?
Yes. We just did.
Well, Eddie, it sounds like
it might be
causing some metabolic abnormalities
that are making it hard
for your body to maintain homeostasis.
You said "causing" and "body,"
and... I lost you.
Listen, Eddie,
we are gonna get you on some meds,
and we are gonna clear that out.
- Yes.
- Never gonna happen.
Will you stop doing that now. Not now.
- Eddie, we're just trying to help you.
- I know.
I know. I'm just,
I'm not actually talking to you, Annie.
Who are you talking to?
I'm just gonna call you back, all right?
Thank you. Thank you, Dan.
Thank you. Thank you, both.
Yeah?
Hey, can you turn
your music down, please?
'Cause I'm having a really hard time.
Whatever.
Yeah, sure, man. Yeah.
- I'll just turn it right down. Sorry.
- Thank you. Thank you.
I was troubled by
what we've been doing.
I get it.
We've all been troubled.
It's the nature of what we do.
But I need you to tell me
who was here with you.
I need that from you.
I can't do that.
We can't fix things unless we begin with
your friend.
The person who was here.
Because they're gonna die.
They're in grave danger.
You know that, right?
They're gonna die
unless we bring them back here,
where you can help to keep them alive.
Hey. Dora.
I promise, from here on in,
we will do things differently.
Will you trust me?
Eddie Brock.
Eddie Brock?
You were our best.
Open it.
No! No!
No! No! No!
Do not open that door.
Stay put.
- Hey, Eddie.
- Who the hell is this guy?
I'm gonna need
Mr. Drake's property back.
- What are you doing?
- I'm...
I'm putting my hands up.
You are making us look bad.
I... No, I am not.
Yes, you are.
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are!
- Why would you do that?
'Cause it is
a very sensible thing to do.
- Eddie...
- I will take care of this myself.
- What?
- Eddie, where's the bug?
Take him down.
I'm so sorry about your friends.
- What is that?
- Not "what." Who.
Shit.
Outstanding.
Now let's bite all their heads off
and pile them up in the corner.
Why would we do that?
Pile of bodies, pile of heads.
What the shit, man?
No! No, no, no!
- What the hell?
- Dude! How did you do that?
Apparently, I have a parasite.
Mr. Drake, our subject
is carrying the Symbiote.
Connecting you to the feed now.
He's achieved symbiosis.
Are you seeing this?
He's achieved symbiosis!
Treece...
Treece, bring me back my creature.
Eddie.
You're not even here, are you?
I'm just seeing things.
It's not real. You're in my head.
'Cause you're just a parasite.
"Parasite"?
You have a brain tumor, Eddie.
I got him. He's in the alley
behind the Schueller Building.
I am sorry that I called you a parasite.
We can discuss this like two men.
What is that? What is that?
What?
Do not let him get away.
Do you understand me, Treece?
Copy. Weapons are armed and ready.
Launch the drones.
Duck.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
This is beyond anything
we thought was possible.
Oh, God, no!
Holy shit!
Treece, do not let him get away.
I've got him.
All ground vehicles, move in.
Target is now eastbound on Grant.
Oh, God! Do something!
What the...
Yeah! We got more friends. Awesome.
No, no, no! No, no!
No! You're out of your mind!
No!
- That is a dead-end!
- Not for us.
Yeah!
I am going to die!
You are not going to die!
That was pretty cool, actually.
I'm not gonna lie...
I got him.
- Bring him home.
- Copy that.
This is incredible.
You have been a serious
pain in the ass for me, Eddie.
Well, you know, I aim to please.
Eyes, lungs, pancreas.
So many snacks, so little time.
SFPD. Don't move!
Get off the car!
My legs.
Oh, my God, my legs were broken.
Now they're not broken.
What is happening?
What the hell are you?
I am Venom.
And you are mine.
You bit somebody's head off.
Fuel in the tank.
Listen carefully, Eddie.
You did not find us.
We found you.
Think of yourself as my ride.
Where are you going?
We need Carlton Drake's rocket.
You remember him.
How do you even know about that?
- I know everything, Eddie.
- You do?
- Everything about you.
- How?
I am inside your head.
You are a loser, Eddie.
Are you gonna eat anybody else?
Most likely.
Oh, God.
That is why we are here.
Cooperate, and you might just survive.
That is the deal.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to San Francisco.
For your safety and comfort,
please remain seated...
Hey, babe. I'm almost home.
- Where's Eddie?
- Why? What's happening?
I got Eddie's labs back,
and it's worse than I thought.
His systems, renal, endocrine,
they're behaving abnormally.
I've never seen anything like it.
What does that mean, Dan?
What are you telling me?
- You need to get him here.
- My God.
- Eddie Brock here. Leave a message.
- Shit.
Where were you
when it left Dr. Skirth's body?
- Where was he?
- I was...
This is the higher life-form.
You stood by and watched while it died.
The arrogance.
Treece, listen to me.
After this, we can't risk killing Brock,
not until we find another suitable host.
I don't want to see you again
unless you have Brock!
Officer, what's happening?
I need to get in there.
- It's my friend's apartment.
- Building's been evacuated.
It's not safe for you to be here, ma'am.
Found another one, Bill.
Get off the streets. Go home.
There's bodies
all over the city tonight.
Bodies?
My God, Eddie, where are you?
Who is Anne? Your pulse has quickened.
That is none of your goddamn business.
Everything of yours
is my business, Eddie.
We have no secrets.
Yeah? Well, then you know
exactly why I'm going here
before we get to your rocket, huh?
Sure. I'm not unreasonable.
Shit. Yeah?
Eddie. Thank God.
Where are you? I need to see you.
No, no, you can't see me.
Eddie, I need you to tell me
where you are. I'm coming to get you.
No, you cannot come anywhere near me.
You cannot come near me right now.
- Richard. Hey, Richard...
- No!
- Eddie?
- No, I gotta go up there.
You know you're not
supposed to be here, Eddie.
I got to get up there, man.
Look, I got love for you, bro,
but no can do.
- There's no such thing as can't.
- I'm sorry, man.
Okay, okay...
Can you just give him this?
- He needs to see what's on it.
- Eddie, please. I really need this job.
- Let's eat his brains.
- No! You do not touch him!
- He is my friend.
- What's wrong with you?
He works three jobs just so that
he can support his family.
- Eddie, what's going on?
- We're leaving.
- "We"?
- Yeah.
- What are you talking about, "we"?
- Just stay back!
Yeah.
- Shit.
- You want up?
Well, why didn't you just say?
- It is peaceful up here.
- I'm not very good with heights.
Your world is not so ugly after all.
I'm almost sorry to see it end.
What does that mean?
Where'd you go? Where did you go?
I got us.
Again? You're gonna get me killed.
You die, I die.
Yeah, well, you can always
just shed my carcass
and exchange it for another one
whenever you need.
Why would I do that?
You are far too good of a match
to throw away so soon.
Plus, I am starting to like you.
You and I are not so different.
Thank you.
Okay.
Here's your evidence.
Jump.
Pussy.
Hands!
On the ground! Now!
Guys, you do not want to do this.
Trust me.
- Mask!
- Copy!
All right, have it your own way.
- Mask!
- Copy.
What the hell is that thing?
What the hell?
Hold your fire!
Flares!
He's there! He's there!
Reload!
Anybody see him?
Does anyone have eyes on him?
Switching to thermal. Seeking target.
I don't have eyes on him.
Where is it?
Flash grenade!
Throw them!
He's in the rafters!
Above!
There he is!
Move, move, move!
No! We do not eat policemen!
Annie! Annie, wait!
- Wait, please.
- What the hell is that?
That's not me. I've been infected.
- Eddie, what's happening?
- He's inside me.
- "He"?
- Yes.
- I know it sounds crazy, but...
- You're sick.
- Eddie, you're really sick.
- No, I am scared!
- And I need help.
- Hospital.
Right now.
I can't go with you. It's not safe.
Get in the car, Eddie.
- In the back.
- I like her. Get in.
I'm out of control.
Dan just needs to do another MRI.
- No MRI.
- No. No. No MRI.
What? Why?
Sound at 4,000 to 6,000 hertz is lethal.
Sound frequency in the MRI
is really harmful for him.
What, so, sound is like his kryptonite?
- Not all sounds.
- And fire.
- Fire. And fire.
- He's talking to you?
Always.
- Are you in pain?
- No.
No, I don't feel anything,
actually, apart from...
I'm hungry all the time.
And you feel sad, do you not, Eddie,
when you are with her?
Get out of my head, man.
You never apologized.
You might not live
to get another chance.
Annie.
I just want to say that
whatever happens,
that I am truly sorry for whatever...
And everything I have ever done to you.
I am truly, truly sorry.
And that I love you.
Eddie...
Now's really not the time.
Let's just keep you alive, okay?
That's nice.
You know, I'm really wet and cold.
Can I wear this?
Yeah, yeah, you can wear
whatever you want.
Thank you.
Hello?
What are you doing here?
Are you lost?
I'm not lost.
Thanks for coming in.
- Eddie, I'm sorry.
- What?
Eddie, I got your labs back,
and your heart has atrophied severely.
Do not listen to him. I can fix it.
I don't want you to fix it.
I can heal you.
Can you fix it?
No. I've never seen
anything like this before.
- This parasite, whatever this is...
- "Parasite"?
- It's eating you from the inside.
- Not a parasite. He's not.
- You're using him up.
- No. She is wrong.
- We need to get you to the ICU.
- Wait.
- I, Eddie, am I dying?
- No!
You're killing him.
They do not know
what they are talking about.
Listen, we don't have a lot of time...
- Oh, God!
- We have to get out of here.
- Stop!
- Oh, God, he's killing you.
I'm killing you. I'm so sorry.
No! Don't do that!
Are you all right? Eddie, I'm sorry.
I had to get him out of you.
What is that?
You were killing me?
What happened to "we," man?
What happened to "we"?
Yeah, look at you now, huh?
Now you're dying, too.
We're done.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Anywhere other than here.
You don't think we have
a little problem on our hands?
Wait, you're not gonna
leave me here with this thing.
You want to tell me
what the hell's going on?
I do. And you're right.
We do need to talk about it,
but I don't know much more than you do.
I guess he had no one else to turn to.
He's a very complicated man.
But, Dan, I promise,
there's nothing going on
between me and Eddie.
I'm not talking
about you and Eddie, Anne.
I'm talking about that.
Dan.
Where is it?
Eddie, Eddie, Eddie.
You can kill me,
'cause I'm dying anyway.
I'm not just gonna kill you.
That wouldn't be any fun.
No, no, no. I'm gonna
rip your tongue out of your face.
Stop. You're bleeding all over my lab.
Go. Go!
- Where is he?
- I don't know.
And you know what? Even if I did,
I wouldn't tell you anyway.
I don't trust you, and you're insane.
- That hurts.
- Sorry.
Long journal entry about that tonight.
You're being dumb, Brock.
I'm not insane.
What's insane is the way
humans choose to live today.
Think about it.
All we do is take, take, take.
It can't go on.
We've brought the planet
to the brink of extinction.
We're parasites. You're a good example.
Think about it. All you do is take.
You took my Symbiote.
You take potshots at a great man
- trying to get something done.
- Who?
Didn't you take from the person
you loved the most,
who trusted you the most? That's insane.
What I've initiated
is a whole new world, a new species.
Man and Symbiote combined.
Let me tell you something, buddy.
All right? Just man-to-man.
Because I have spent
a significant amount of time, all right,
with one of these creatures up my ass.
It's not a lot of fun.
And then I find out, all along,
that they're killing you.
This is the last time I'm asking you.
- Where is my Symbiote?
- I have no idea.
- Where is he?
- Oh, my God!
Where's Venom?
That is the ugliest-looking thing
I have ever seen.
You know, Brock, I have no use for you.
Treece! Come and clean up your mess.
He has one up his ass, too.
Your friends, the others, I apologize.
I tried to keep them alive.
There are more of us. Millions more.
They will follow wherever I lead.
Where we lead.
Yes, "we."
But first, we must retrieve them.
I can take care of that.
Yeah, what you gonna do,
you gonna walk me to death?
Shut up.
Not so tough without your friend.
Did your mama not love you?
God damn it!
I guess it pays to be a specialist, huh?
You know, it doesn't matter
if you kill me anyway,
because there's something
way bigger afoot
in this world than you and me.
Much bigger than me.
And it's much, much bigger than you.
Karma's a bitch.
I don't believe in karma.
Hi, Eddie.
Oh, no.
I just bit that guy's head off.
I know, I know.
I've been there, too. It's not fun.
- The one with Drake is Riot.
- Who's Riot?
Riot is what you would call
a team leader.
He has an arsenal of weapons.
- Drake's got his own Symbiote.
- He is unstoppable.
- Great.
- We have got to go!
Go where? Where we going?
- Well, I'm coming with you.
- No!
It's going to get ugly.
- Well, she can fight ugly. Trust me.
- Yeah, I can fight ugly.
Not today.
That's bullshit!
This is not a simulation.
Well, the flight team
aren't prepped yet.
I'll be piloting the spacecraft.
- You?
- Yes, me.
How long?
We're loading the probe
and running diagnostics.
But even fully automated,
you can't pilot that craft all alone.
I'm not alone.
God damn it! What the hell
happened there? We just left Annie.
It is not safe for her.
If we do not stop Riot,
he will come back here
with millions more of my kind.
Millions? What, you were gonna
take the rocket,
and you were gonna come back
here with an invasion force?
Then what were you gonna do,
you were gonna go feed
- on a whole planet?
- Yes!
But it is different now, Eddie.
I have decided to stay.
On my planet,
I am kind of a loser, like you.
- But here, we could be more.
- Excuse me?
And I'm getting to like it here.
You like us now, do you, huh?
However, there will be nothing left
to like if we do not stop that rocket.
I see. Right. When it comes to
being completely annihilated,
- then it's back to "we."
- It is "we."
Like it or not,
it is going to take both of us.
Cut the bullshit.
What really made you change your mind?
You. You did, Eddie.
Scrub diagnostics.
- Sir?
- Did you hear me? Initiate the launch.
T-minus five minutes to launch.
Auto sequence has been initiated.
Shit.
T-minus four minutes, 30 seconds.
Oh, Jesus! You can take this guy, right?
He has got shit you have never seen.
What does that mean?
What are our chances?
Pretty much zero.
Fuck it. Well, let's go save the planet.
T-minus four minutes.
Initiate orbiter aerosurface profile.
Venom. Get in the rocket.
No. We won't let you destroy this world.
Then die.
- Holy shit!
- Told you.
T-minus three minutes.
You have a strong host.
But not strong enough.
T-minus two minutes, 30 seconds.
Eddie.
Drake, stop!
Told you I could fight ugly.
T-minus one minute.
You're too late.
This is the next stage...
You talk too much.
T-minus 30 seconds.
You are nothing.
Ten seconds.
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Liftoff.
Traitor!
Have a nice life.
Goodbye, Eddie.
Venom, no!
Thanks for sticking by me, Annie.
Thanks for saving me.
So, how you feeling after all that?
I feel great. Awesome.
Yeah, I'm thinking of suing, though.
You want to prosecute?
You're in luck.
I've decided to work pro bono.
I'm joining
the public defenders' office.
You're a good person, Annie.
What about you? What are you gonna do?
The network asked me
to bring the show back,
and they want to start
with a piece on Drake.
Really? So, what did you say?
I'm not into it. I want to
concentrate on the written word.
I scored the interview of a lifetime.
- Yeah? Who?
- You're gonna have to read it.
Like everyone else.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm sorry about Venom.
Hey...
Do you want to talk about that kiss?
That? You call that a kiss...
No, that was...
That was your buddy's idea.
Right. Well, that is good to know.
- It did feel kind of great, though.
- What?
I mean, the...
- The power?
- Yeah. When it's, you know...
- Inside you?
- You know what I mean.
Okay.
Hey, Eddie?
We're not gonna
tell Dan about this. Okay?
Look at her. She has no idea
we are going to get her back.
No, I don't think so.
- Sorry, what was that?
- We're not gonna tell Dan.
Eddie, is there something
you want to tell me?
- Nope.
- You belong with us, Annie.
Eddie, are you sure?
Good Lord, look at that.
Look at the time. I have to go.
- Hey, it's nice seeing you.
- Yeah.
You take care, all right?
- Yeah, you take care of yourself.
- Bye.
Hey. Don't give up on her.
Either of you.
We won't.
- Who is that guy?
- Okay.
Wait. This thing looks delicious.
I have absolutely no problem
with you sticking around,
but if you do, we're gonna have to
have some ground rules, all right?
You cannot just go around
eating anybody that you want to.
- I cannot?
- No, you cannot.
All right, we need to...
We need to reiterate this.
There are good people
in this world, a lot of them.
And then there are bad people.
You have to tell the difference.
The deal is, you will only ever
be allowed to touch,
harm, hurt, possibly, very possibly,
eat very, very bad people,
but never, ever, ever good people.
All right?
- Fine.
- Good.
But how does one tell the difference?
Well, it's super simple.
I mean, you just have to...
You can intuit it, you can sense it.
Sometimes you can even feel it.
Whatever you say.
But can we get something to eat now?
Otherwise, your liver, it's starting
to look really, really good and juicy.
Yeah. Definitely.
I know a place down here.
Hey, Mrs. C.
How you doing, Eddie?
Ain't nothing changed
but the weather. You know.
No.
So, what culinary delights
will tickle the pickle tonight?
Tater tots and chocolate.
Right. Okay, no problem.
The payment's due, Chen.
- Please. I can't keep doing this.
- Now.
- Bad guy, right?
- Yep.
You come in here again...
In fact, you go anywhere in this city,
preying on innocent people,
and we will find you
and eat both your arms
- and then both of your legs.
- No, no.
And then we will eat your face
right off your head. Do you understand?
- Please...
- Yes.
So, you will be this armless, legless,
faceless thing, won't you,
rolling down the street,
like a turd in the wind?
- Do you feel me?
- What the hell are you?
We are Venom.
- On second thought...
- Please.
Eddie? What was that?
I have a parasite. Yeah.
Night, Mrs. Chen.
- "Parasite"?
- Yeah.
It's a term of endearment, that's all.
- Apologize!
- No.
- All right, fine.
I'm sorry.
So, what do you want to do now?
The way I see it,
we can do whatever we want.
I need you to stay quiet.
This is a "me" thing.
It is not a "we" thing.
- You got that?
- Fine, but make it quick.
Open on five.
Go. Opening up.
You ask me, they're dumb
to let him call the shots.
Second he asked
for you to interview him,
I'd have shut that shit down.
Yeah, you know the FBI.
They're just taking advantage
of the one and only time
he'll ever speak to anyone.
They're hoping that I might help them
identify some additional bodies.
FBI don't work
up close and personal with him.
The FBI will have to identify you,
if you don't follow the rules.
Hey, Red! I got a visitor for you.
- Hi, Eddie.
- Hey.
Do you mind if we forego the whole
creepy serial killer thing here?
Sure, it's good with me.
I mean, I can turn it on if you want.
I can talk about the Dadaist patterns
of arterial spray.
I bet you can.
Tough to see you in this light, Eddie.
Come on over.
All right.
I'm here.
When I get out of here, and I will,
there's gonna be carnage.
I'm sorry, Mr. Parker.
I want to do what you asked.
I really do.
But... I'm sorry.
I can't do this without you.
Hey, kid...
What was...
What?
No.
Who are you?
What are you doing over there?
Freeze! PDNY.
Kid, freeze!
You're kidding me right now?
Hey, kid. Drop the body.
Somebody stop that train!
Sorry.
...looks like a child
dressed like Spider-Man,
dragging a homeless corpse
behind a train.
- Who are you?
- Why are you trying to kill me?
- I'm not. I'm trying to save you.
Hey, maybe you guys can go around?
All right. Thanks, New York.
Modify by Blue-Bird™
Sync & corrections by Blue-Bird™